This is Tang Hongtu.
Second Master Tang.
Tang.(Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
Second Master Tang.
The head of the number one Tang family in Bian Shui.
It's me.
To be able to work for Second Master...
is my honor.
May I ask what you want me to do?
I want you to go back to Old Street.
Get everyone to sign the demolition contract...
with our Tang Group.
Second Master...
That kid Zhao Fengsheng saved...
has already woken up.
If I go back now...
the neighbors will probably investigate me...
What are you afraid of?
Those two idiots who did the kidnapping...
Master Mu has already taken care of them for you.
As long as you deny it to the end...
who dares to call you a trafficker?
Chen Xiaobei.
Do you think I called you here...
to discuss this with you?
If you don't handle this well...
you...
will go down to join your two brothers.
Master Mu...
Second Master...
Have mercy!
Darn it.
I'll do it.
Xiaobei.
These past few days...
you've really worked hard.
It's nothing.
Our houses are really old, right?
They'll need renovating sooner or later.
Coincidentally...
I know this big boss.
No problem, no problem.
Chen Xiaobei!
This trafficker dares to come back?
Let's teach him a lesson!
I've also looked at the contract.
I just wanted to help the neighbors...
renovate their houses.
Build new buildings, live in new homes.
Chen Xiaobei!
Come here!
Let go!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
What have you learned from Zhao Fengsheng?
Be polite to the neighbors.
Uncle Snake...
This jerk framed Fengsheng.
Today he must explain himself to everyone.
It really was a misunderstanding.
Didn't we already explain it clearly?
You think saying "misunderstanding" settles it?
How do we account for the neighbors wronging Fengsheng?
I apologize.
I'll accept any punishment you give.
You said it.
Don't play dumb.
You've been hanging out with the Traffickers' Village
people for a long time.
Xiaoxiao was kidnapped by you.
Brother Fengsheng.
This is a huge misunderstanding.
That day, I saw Xiaoxiao being kidnapped.
In a moment of panic,
I thought you were with them.
Brother.
I
have already heard.
You and Gangzi took care of the Traffickers' Village guys
and even stormed the Ghost Face Hall.
You're heroes of our Old Street.
Right?
Yeah.
Don't call me brother.
You're not worthy.
You want to put on an act for me?
Brother Fengsheng.
I don't know what you're talking about.
About the misunderstanding,
it was my fault.
I apologize to you.
I'll kowtow to you.
Fengsheng.
Forgive others when you can.
Xiaobei.
Back then, wasn't he
also worried about Xiaoxiao?
Auntie Wang, don't you get it?
He's a trafficker.
Don't talk nonsense.
Fengsheng.
The misunderstanding about you being a trafficker,
the whole Old Street knows.
Besides, you didn't lose anything.
Let's just drop this matter.
I didn't lose anything?
We're all neighbors here.
Why make such an ugly scene?
I'm not trying to make a scene.
Think about it yourselves.
Every time he's about to be exposed,
he disappears and hides.
He wasn't here when the Ghost Face Hall surrounded Old Street.
He wasn't here when Xiaoxiao woke up.
Isn't that clear enough?
Brother Fengsheng.
A colossal misunderstanding.
These past few days,
I've been helping the neighbors
find opportunities to get rich.
Opportunities to get rich?
The neighbors have all joined the Chinese Association.
What else do we need you to arrange?
Selling goods earns just a pittance.
Look at Auntie Wang's hands.
Even with calluses this thick,
can she earn enough for an apartment?
Young Bei is also thinking of the neighbors.
He contacted a big boss from outside
to redevelop our Old Street.
What?
Redevelop?
What big boss?
Explain yourself clearly.
Second Master Tang from the Tang Group.
He said
our Old Street has huge development potential.
He plans to acquire Old Street
and turn it into high-end apartments.
Tang Hongtu wants to demolish Old Street.
He calls it redevelopment.
And on a separate plot nearby,
he'll build new houses for the neighbors.
Plus a large sum of demolition compensation.
And compensation money.
That's good news!
The neighbors will have a better life.
Such a good deal...
what's in it for the Tang Group?
Boss Tang
naturally wants to develop Bian Shui better.
He says
as Bian Shui's leading enterprise,
this is how to attract foreign investment
and grow bigger.
Does Uncle Snake and the neighbors know?
Of course, it's been explained clearly.
Xiaobei.
Come on, let's go.
Tell Auntie the details again.
Right, right.
Let's go.
Fengsheng.
Why did you pull me back?
I still think
this guy Chen Xiaobei
is a bit suspicious.
Who cares if Chen Xiaobei is suspicious?
Demolition isn't a bad thing.
Think about our Old Street houses.
How many years old are they?
We still have to use public toilets.
What a hassle.
I know that, of course.
Our Old Street has no real business,
no profitable industry.
Tang Hongtu spending big money to buy Old Street...
I still can't figure it out.
Why overthink it?
As long as the Tang Group pays up,
we won't lose out.
Right?
Once we have the money,
Er Ni's mother
won't stand in the way of your marriage.
We're talking serious business.
Why bring up Er Ni?
Understood, understood.
I'll have the guys go ask around
to see what's really going on.
Is Brother Fengsheng home?
You jerk!
You dare show your face?
What's wrong?
Here to kowtow, apologize, and admit your mistake?
Brother Fengsheng.
It was all a misunderstanding before.
Today, Second Master himself sent word.
He'd like to invite you to the Tang Group for a chat.
Tang Hongtu is inviting me?
Yes.
Second Master said
you, Zhao Fengsheng, are a man of courage.
You wouldn't even dare to meet him.
A provocation.
Fengsheng.
Don't fall for it.
Tang Hongtu is a man who holds sway over Bian Shui.
He has no need to play dirty tricks with me.
And I happen to want to meet him.
Let's go. Lead the way.
Brother Gangzi
Second Master only invited one person.
So,
let's go.
Director Wang, you better win big today.
Playing, huh?
You've gotten prettier again.
The Tang Group even has a casino in Bian Shui.
Master Mu.
Please lend me another five hundred thousand.
I'm sure I can win it all back.
Master Mu.
Lend you more?
Your house,
your car,
and your beautiful wife
are already mortgaged.
What do you have left to borrow against?
Master Mu.
You...
Look, how much am I worth?
I'll mortgage myself, Master Mu.
A life is the cheapest thing there is.
You two,
take him to the coal mine to dig.
A hundred a day.
Until his debt is paid.
A hundred bucks a day?
When will I ever get out?
Master Mu!
Zhao Fengsheng.
You dare show your face in front of me?
Master Mu.
Your new look is so cool.
How can you be so darn annoying?
You know what?
I'll settle the score for this eye
right now.
Master Mu.
Second Master wants to see Zhao Fengsheng.
I know.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't be standing here talking nonsense.
Weren't you a dog for the Ghost Face Hall?
Now you're a dog for the Tang family?
Are you addicted to being a dog?
You!
Didn't Uncle Gui Lang teach you how to talk to me?
Uncle Gui Lang?
He's already dead.
Your backer is gone.
And you're still acting so tough with me?
You did it?
He was getting senile.
So I had no choice
but to show some filial piety
and put him out of his misery.
After all,
Uncle Gui Lang and I were acquainted.
I'm considering
whether to gouge out your other eye
to see him off properly.
Zhao Fengsheng.
Don't look at me like that.
If Second Master didn't want to see you,
I'd finish you off right now.
Can't be bothered with your nonsense.
Come with me to see Second Master.
Killing the Ghost Wolf leader,
taking in Mu Jinfu,
demolishing Old Street...
This series of moves
seems to be all Tang Hongtu's doing.
What does this Second Master Tang want?
I've long heard of Old Street's Zhao Fengsheng.
Brother Shengzi.
I've been wanting to meet you for a long time.
This sofa of yours is comfortable.
Must have cost a lot, right?
A sofa is nothing.
As long as you, Brother Shengzi,
are willing to join my Tang Group,
villas, luxury cars, beautiful women—you'll have it all.
So you're recruiting me, Second Master?
That's right.
You, Zhao Fengsheng, with just two or three men,
managed to take down Traffickers' Village
and even bravely stormed the Ghost Face Hall.
It's truly impressive.
I admire you.
You flatter me, Second Master.
After you took over the Ghost Face Hall,
you're the biggest local power in Bian Shui.
There's no need to recruit me.
You probably don't want me leading the neighbors to cause trouble
and delay your demolition project, right?
Brother Shengzi gets straight to the point.
I do have that intention.
Second Master.
You say our Old Street is just a piece of worthless land.
No industry to speak of.
Why are you so fixated on it?
Expanding industrial investment,
increasing our presence in Bian Shui,
attracting foreign capital...
This is
our strategic goal
as the Tang Group.
I don't understand.
Brother Shengzi isn't well-versed in business.
That's understandable.
But you just need to remember one thing:
Having our Tang Group develop Old Street
is nothing but beneficial for all of you.
And what if I disagree?